Now, handling audio focus in our app is going to be a pretty
在应用中处理 Audio Focus 将是非常重要的
significant code change.
代码更改
So before you go off on your own, let's walk through the major decisions
在操作之前 我们先讲解下你在使用 AudioManager API 时
you'll need to make when using the Audio Manager API.
需要作出的重大决策
So remember, API just refers to the classes and methods that are offered by
注意 API 是指 Android 框架向开发者提供的
the Android framework that you as a developer can use.
类和方法
Now let's start by requesting audio focus from the AudioManager.
我们先从 AudioManager 请求 Audio Focus
In order to begin playing the audio on the app.
以便开始在应用上播放音频
In the last quiz, we found that we need to call the requestAudioFocus method and
在上一道测试题中 我们发现我们需要调用 requestAudioFocus 方法
it requires three inputs, onAudioFocusChangeListener object,
该方法需要以下三个输入：一个 onAudioFocusChangeListener 对象
a streamType and a durationHint.
streamType 和 a durationHint
So these last two inputs here, the streamType and
最后两个输入 streamType 和
the durationHint are integers.
durationHint 是整型类型
Now when we call this method requestAudioFocus what should we pass in
当我们调用 requestAudioFocus 方法时 我们应该传入什么
as a stream type which will be our second parameter and
作为 streamType 它是我们的第二个参数
this refers to the type of audio they we're playing?
指的是我们要播放的音频的类型
So is this a song or ring tone?
是歌曲还是铃声？
And for the second question, which we pass in as the durationHint?
第二个问题 我们应该传入什么作为 durationHint？
So the third parameter.
即第三个参数
And this refers to how long we need audio focus for.
指的是 Audio Focus 所需的时长
So do we need it for a short period time or a long period of time?
是需要很短的时间还是很长时间？
So as a hint, both of these answer choices should be integers, and
提示下 这两个答案都应该是整型
more specifically they should be integer constants that have already been defined
更具体地说 应该是已经在 AudioManager 类中
in the AudioManager class.
定义的整型常量
So in the reference documentation for the AudioManager class, if we scroll
在 AudioManager 类的参考文档中
down to this public constant section and then go down a little bit further.
滚动到这个公开常量部分 然后再往下滚动一点点
So these are all the possible stream types that you can
这些都是可以传入 requestAudioFocus 方法的
pass into a requestAudioFocus method.
可能 streamType
And you can refer to them as audiomanager.stream or
可以引用为 AudioManager.STREAM
audiomanager.stream.DTMF and so on and
AudioManager.STREAM.DTMF 等等
so on and the descriptions for each stream type is on the right column.
左列给出了每个 streamType 的说明
So let's click into the stream along constant to get some more details.
我们点开 STREAM_ALARM 变量了解下详情
Now remember a constant is a fixed value the never changes, and
变量是指值永远不会变化的固定值
by convention we name the variable in all capital letters.
按照惯例 变量名称全大写
So it's often used to communicate a certain state.
通常用来表示某种状态
So this case are stream alone has a value of four and
这里 STREAM_ALARM 的值为 4
that will never change.
永远不会改变
So when we pass in this constant value to the AudioManager,
当我们向 AudioManager 传入这个常量值时
it knows that we mean this particular stream type.
它就会知道我们指的是这种特定的 streamType
All right so this takes care of it for our stream types.
这些就是关于 streamType 的信息
What about our durationHint?
那么 durationHint 呢？
Let's navigate over here to requestAudioFocus method and
我们转到 requestAudioFocus 方法
notice here the different valid options for
注意 方法说明部分列出了
durationHint are listed in the method description.
durationHint 的不同有效选项
So we have different ones such as audioFocus_Gain_Transient,
例如 AUDIOFOCUS_GAIN_TRANSIENT
audioFocus_Gain_Transient_May_Duck and
AUDIOFOCUS_GAIN_TRANSIENT_MAY_DUCK
then a couple other ones and each of these have explanations
以及其他几个选项 每个都提供了解释说明
to help you choose which one is the appropriate one to pick.
使你能够选择最合适的选项
So feel free to search online for
如果你在回答这两个问题时需要帮助
tutorials if you need help answering these two questions.
请上网搜索下相关教程
And I'd like you to fill out your answers here and then continue on.
请将答案填在方框中 然后继续